{
    "id": "3dd01687703c46b6adf71594b3f25f70",
    "title": "In spite of, despite, however, though and although",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8445b406875d437882c2341c1bb3b87a",
            "title": "In Spite Of, Despite, However, Though, Although",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We went out ………………….. the rain.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "despite",
                        "in spite of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We went out ………………….. it was raining.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "however",
                        "in spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The judge sent her to prison ……………….. the fact that she had very small children.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "despite",
                        "however",
                        "though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… I didn’t enjoy the movie, I watched it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I enjoyed the party ……………….. I didn’t know anybody there.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "however",
                        "in spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I bought the watch, ……………… it was expensive.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "however",
                        "though",
                        "despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "John didn’t come ……………….., everybody else did.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "despite",
                        "however"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… the government refuses to admit it, it has failed to revive the economy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "Despite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He failed ………………… his hard work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "though",
                        "in spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn’t like her rude behavior. ………………, I said nothing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Despite",
                        "Though",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}